Guide to the photograph album Orientreise 1898 AD.MC.062
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- A blank page in the album 'Orientreise, 1898'., AD_MC_062_ref54; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_062)
  Istanbul, Turkey; Palestine; Syria; Italy; Egypt; Lebanon; Greece
- The inside back cover of the album 'Orientreise, 1898'., AD_MC_062_ref55; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_062)
  Palestine; Greece; Egypt; Lebanon; Syria; Italy; Istanbul, Turkey
- The back cover of the album 'Orientreise, 1898'., AD_MC_062_ref56; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_062)
  Palestine; Syria; Lebanon; Istanbul, Turkey; Greece; Egypt; Italy
- Inhaltsverzeichnis (table of contents), accompanying the album 'Orientreise, 1898', page 1 of 3, AD_MC_062_ref57; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_062)
- Inhaltsverzeichnis (table of contents), accompanying the album 'Orientreise, 1898', page 2 of 3, AD_MC_062_ref58; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_062)
- Inhaltsverzeichnis (table of contents), accompanying the album 'Orientreise, 1898', page 3 of 3, AD_MC_062_ref59; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_062)
- Momentaufnahmen auf der Orientreise (snapshots on the Orient trip). Accompanying booklet to the album 'Orientreise, 1898', listing locations photographed, page 1 of 18, AD_MC_062_ref60; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_062)
- Momentaufnahmen auf der Orientreise (snapshots on the Orient trip). Accompanying booklet to the album 'Orientreise, 1898', listing locations photographed, page 2 of 18, AD_MC_062_ref61; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_062)
- Momentaufnahmen auf der Orientreise (snapshots on the Orient trip). Accompanying booklet to the album 'Orientreise, 1898', listing locations photographed, page 3 of 18, AD_MC_062_ref62; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_062)
- Momentaufnahmen auf der Orientreise (snapshots on the Orient trip). Accompanying booklet to the album 'Orientreise, 1898', listing locations photographed, page 4 of 18, AD_MC_062_ref63; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_062)
- Momentaufnahmen auf der Orientreise (snapshots on the Orient trip). Accompanying booklet to the album 'Orientreise, 1898', listing locations photographed, page 5 of 18, AD_MC_062_ref64; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_062)
- Momentaufnahmen auf der Orientreise (snapshots on the Orient trip). Accompanying booklet to the album 'Orientreise, 1898', listing locations photographed, page 6 of 18, AD_MC_062_ref65; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_062)
- Momentaufnahmen auf der Orientreise (snapshots on the Orient trip). Accompanying booklet to the album 'Orientreise, 1898', listing locations photographed, page 7 of 18, AD_MC_062_ref66; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_062)
- Momentaufnahmen auf der Orientreise (snapshots on the Orient trip). Accompanying booklet to the album 'Orientreise, 1898', listing locations photographed, page 8 of 18, AD_MC_062_ref67; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_062)
- Momentaufnahmen auf der Orientreise (snapshots on the Orient trip). Accompanying booklet to the album 'Orientreise, 1898', listing locations photographed, page 9 of 18, AD_MC_062_ref68; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_062)
- Momentaufnahmen auf der Orientreise (snapshots on the Orient trip). Accompanying booklet to the album 'Orientreise, 1898', listing locations photographed, page 10 of 18, AD_MC_062_ref69; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_062)
- Momentaufnahmen auf der Orientreise (snapshots on the Orient trip). Accompanying booklet to the album 'Orientreise, 1898', listing locations photographed, page 11 of 18, AD_MC_062_ref70; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_062)
- Momentaufnahmen auf der Orientreise (snapshots on the Orient trip). Accompanying booklet to the album 'Orientreise, 1898', listing locations photographed, page 12 of 18, AD_MC_062_ref71; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_062)
- Momentaufnahmen auf der Orientreise (snapshots on the Orient trip). Accompanying booklet to the album 'Orientreise, 1898', listing locations photographed, page 13 of 18, AD_MC_062_ref72; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_062)
- Momentaufnahmen auf der Orientreise (snapshots on the Orient trip). Accompanying booklet to the album 'Orientreise, 1898', listing locations photographed, page 14 of 18, AD_MC_062_ref73; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_062)
- Momentaufnahmen auf der Orientreise (snapshots on the Orient trip). Accompanying booklet to the album 'Orientreise, 1898', listing locations photographed, page 15 of 18, AD_MC_062_ref74; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_062)
- Momentaufnahmen auf der Orientreise (snapshots on the Orient trip). Accompanying booklet to the album 'Orientreise, 1898', listing locations photographed, page 16 of 18, AD_MC_062_ref75; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_062)
- Momentaufnahmen auf der Orientreise (snapshots on the Orient trip). Accompanying booklet to the album 'Orientreise, 1898', listing locations photographed, page 17 of 18, AD_MC_062_ref76; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_062)
- Momentaufnahmen auf der Orientreise (snapshots on the Orient trip). Accompanying booklet to the album 'Orientreise, 1898', listing locations photographed, page 18 of 18, AD_MC_062_ref77; 1 Photographic Prints (Box AD_MC_062)